(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-26T22:52:55.357271",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Yeah, are you there?
You're a super girl
(Justice just like that, Justice get get that)
If you're feeling trapped, send out a signal right above!
(Gesundheit!)
We'll find you, set you free then you can sign up for the club!
(Innit!)
Danger, fun fun fun
No sad, say bye bye
(Minna happiness, minna happiness)
The frig? I'm big! My strong strong muscle
They see me run, it's no miracle
You are shining so bright!
Do your dancing, let's fight!
You can be a super super girl
I'm the super! (Hey!) Duper!
(Supernova super girl)
Super! (Hey!) Duper!
Come sing with us, beating villains for fun <3 it
(I'm super girl)
Put on your antennas, get your super girl fit
(You're super girl)
Super! (Hey!) Duper!
Supernova super girl
I always want a pizza, stack those fries up to the sky
(Ciao ciao)
You lot say whatcha think about us hittin' town tonight?
(Justice!)
Feeling happy time
No sad, say bye bye
(Motto maniac, Justice just like that)
So stomp, stomp, stomp your feet to this beat
Cuz we are space, no no gravity!
You are shining so bright!
Do your dancing, let's fight!
You can be a super super girl
I'm the super! (Hey!) Duper!
(Supernova super girl)
Super! (Hey!) Duper!
I know you're feeling so super bad
You don't have depression, you're just super sad
We are change the world, that's hope!
If you doubt, hope you explode!
Justice loud, Justice proud and we keep telling you!
(K, adlib!)
We are super! (Hey!) Duper!
(Supernova super girl)
Super! (Hey!) Duper!
Justice we are Justice, make the baddies go boom!
(I'm super girl)
Come on, come on, baby, rocket ship to the moon!
(You're super girl)
I'm the super! (Hey!) Duper!
Supernova super girl
Mom / Jenna Roehrs
J / Gemma
Hey, why were you taking Raora?
No, I wasn't!
Raora already helps me laugh, it's... first come, first served.
What are you even talking about?
No! Mine! Mine! Mine! She's mine, man!
Don't take... No, it's mine!
Raora's mine now! No, mine! Mine! Mine! Mine!
J! What on Earth are you playing over here?
The Jealousy Game.
The Jealousy Game?
And shouldn't you play something more appropriate for a five-year-old?
Mom, I'm five, and this is what five-year-olds do, and at least this was funny.
Oh, you and your father are definitely having a conversation about this later.
All righty, it's time for your favorite thing: Justice!
Justice! Justice!
We are Justice.
They make lots of trouble.
What?
Oh, it started!
Justice! Justice!
How to Protect Justice!
Members of Justice are expected to possess strength, sound judgment, and an unwavering sense of justice.
In this training video, you will learn the fundamental skills and exercises required of every Justice member.
Now, join us and say it together: For Justice!
The first training is a body search...
...conducted immediately after securing a subject. Even the slightest oversight can lead to serious incidents or the destruction of evidence...
...making this one of the most critical police procedures.
Can Justice keep their emotions in check under any circumstances and carry out a precise body search to completion?
Stop, ma'am! No further! No further, it is...
...policy, and I'll be conducting a body search!
Come here, ma'am. Yes, body search, you hear?
You really insist?
Over here, over here, over here, ma'am!
Do you have any electronics, tablets, laptops, devices?
Turn around here, ma'am! Arms up!
All right, spread your arms, there we go. Wonderful, wonderful. All right.
What is this?
You know, Chatini. You see, my Chatini, they're always hungry and they really want some food.
So I always have an emergency cucumber!
Emergency rations. I see, I see, I see.
We can't have that on the premises, I'm sorry.
I take care of them.
All right, spread your legs, ma'am, over here.
Over here, ma'am. Over here, right here.
What are you gonna do if I don't do it?
Uh, probably arrest you, put you in jail for many years, and...
Arrest me? Really?
You're gonna arrest me? What are you gonna do?
What if I check on you instead?
No, that's my job, ma'am. My job, over here, ma'am!
All right, stand there! What is...
...this?
I like cooking. Would you like something? Maybe I can cook something for you?
Ma'am, I'm a professional, no dating on the job!
Don't you want a little bit of pasta? I'm so good at making pasta!
Pasta? Well, I am a bit hungry...
Hey, hey, hey! Stop trying to tempt me, stop trying to tempt me!
All right, stand here! Stand here, ma'am! Right here, now!
She's kind of hot...
Three, two, one, arms out! All right...
...and what is this?
How did you find that?
That's a... that's a Chatini jetpack! Oh, no one should see this, get out of here!
Ma'am! You just threw that small... little creature!
Don't worry about it!
All right, anyway, what is this?
Are you gonna punish me?
You have a lot of food-related items on you, ma'am.
Ma'am, you have a lot of food-related items.
Yeah, please, please eat that before you go.
Do you want a little bit too?
No, ma'am, I'm on the job. I'm on the job!
Anyway, ma'am, arms up! Come here, over here.
What are you gonna do if I don't do it? What, do you punish me or something?
Uh, maybe if you don't come over here right now.
I'm behaving!
Not gonna do it! What are you gonna do about it?
Gonna make you do ten push-ups outside of this training.
Maybe I can do some squats for you?
What is this?
No, not this one!
What? No! I can explain!
You know, I'm an artist, and...
Ah, right, an artist. I can explain! I can explain!
Anatomy book. That's my anatomy book!
Ma'am, you are way too suspicious!
You are under arrest! And also...
Under arrest? Really?
...for having Chatinis with jetpacks, that is unbelievable!
You are a bad, bad kitty! You are a bad kitty, come here!
All right, you are under arrest!
Oh, yes I am!
Yeah, that was really good, Raora.
Are we going to jail? That was it, yeah.
That's it for the training, Raora. Are you gonna bring me to jail?
We can share a cell together! Raora, no, we're done with the training!
Hey, we're done with the video! Hey, you need to arrest me! Let me in!
All right then.
Officer Cecilia Immergreen will be conducting...
Conducting the body search!
Stop right there!
Hands up in the air!
Wait, I didn't do anything wrong!
I'm warning you! Do I have your consent to do a body search on you?
No, no...
Do I have your consent? Do I... Okay.
Okay, let us see what you have here!
What are these charges?!
What's this?
Nothing!
Hey, that's mine! Why did you take that from me?
No, it's not! We've never met before! Why would I take something from you?
No! I can't believe you would steal! What a thief!
I didn't steal it! It was given to me!
Stand still! Hands up in the air!
No! Ah!
What... what's this then?
There's nothing wrong with having that in my pocket! It's a Gran, we're buddies! We're friends!
Does it live under humane living conditions?
Yes, it lives in a nice little shoebox and it's really happy there! So that's why you should not arrest me, Officer!
Can you believe him?
What's this?
Wait, Otomo? Why do you have Otomo?!
For no reason! Are they friends? They're friends!
He was on a playdate, obviously! He came to visit the shoebox, so that's why!
Am I free to go, Officer?
I'm starting to think that maybe... maybe it's okay. Let me see one more time.
Ah! Stop, ah! What's... what's this?!
Nothing... It's nothing.
Can't a girl have some BL in her pocket?
Kimi ni Dunk?!
Can't a girl have some hobby? Am I not allowed to read?
Stop tickling, that's not nice! What's this?!
Another one?!
This one is a cat boy... Have you heard of that really awesome manga where whenever...
Okay, okay... On the floor! Get on the floor!
On the floor?! Get down!
Stop making those noises! What's this?!
What's this one then?
So this one... I really like this one. These two men right here, one of them is an Omega, another one is an Alpha, it's called the Omegaverse.
They don't actually turn into wolves here, it's called pack dynamics, and one of them is really dominant, and the other one is really submissive.
And then one of them can get pregnant! Hello? Are you listening, Officer?
Officer? One of them gets pregnant, and it's really...
The next training is: Apprehension Training!
This is a critical close-quarters task in the field,
requiring officers to approach and subdue a target swiftly.
However, unexpected behavior on-site can sometimes shake one's judgment.
Can Justice successfully and reliably subdue the target?
Gigi and Raora's Apprehension Training! You have 3 minutes! Begin!
Yeah! You're going down, criminal scum!
No! Ah!
Put your arms behind your back!
Why would you do that?!
Look at my tail! Look at my tail!
I'm gonna show her who's winning.
Hey, Gigi! Don't fall for that!
You know, you kind of hurt me...
Show me your back!
Now you have the right to remain silent!
No, no, no! You don't want to hurt me, do you?
You're a criminal, so I'm gonna have to touch you!
I'm gonna have to put you in jail!
Oh, that's mean! Why would you put me in jail, Gigi?
Oh, stop! Stop!
Apprehend her!
Help! Help! She's killing me! She's killing me!
Get off! Get off! Get off!
Gigi, why do you want to touch my tail? Hey, that's my tail!
Show me your tail!
Ah! Stop! Stop!
You're a criminal! You're a criminal! You're a criminal!
Down, Raora!
Don't look! Don't look!
Get back down! Get down!
Get down! Where are you going?
Oh, that hurt! That hurt, right?
No, I wouldn't touch you. I will touch you.
I will touch you! I will hurt you! Lie down!
Lie down! You're a criminal! You're a criminal, so you have to lie down!
You have to do what I say 'cause I'm a police!
You have to do what I say 'cause I'm the police!
Wait, I have something here. Hold on.
Oh, my clothes! My...
I'm trying! I'm trying!
I'm trying!
Get back on the ground!
Oh, you wanna be here next to me?
Why do you watch me?!
Get off! Get off me!
Both of them are terrible at this!
Ew, get off me!
Kiss me! Kiss me! Kiss me! Kiss me!
Did I win? Guys, did I win?
Okay, okay, okay. That's enough, that's enough! That's enough!
Um, I don't know, guys... How was that apprehension?
Did I win? Who do you think won this?" "Did I win?" "Wow...
And the winner is..." "Did I win?
Wait, this is about apprehension training, there's no winner.
Okay, so did you do a good job apprehending her?" "I am still free!
In the end, you apprehended her." "Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was in a very..." "I got her in a leg lock and everything!
I think she's correct." "You definitely interlocked...
Hey!
Hey! Hey, hey! Stop it! Stop it, Gigi!
You know, I disqualify Gigi, so Gigi's the winner!" "Yay!
Yeah, Gigi! Well done! You apprehended...
No, no, I think you won!" "Yeah, Gigi, that was really good." "I think you won, too.
Hey, hey! Not without my consent!" "Okay, okay!
Elizabeth and Cecilia apprehension training!
You have 3 minutes! Are you ready?
One, 1 second, here we go.
Flame on!
Flame on!" "I'm ready!
Flame on!" "Flame on!
Are you guys ready now?" "We're ready!" "Yes!
Okay! 3, 2, 1, start!
Suspect! Suspect, stop right there!
I am Evil Elizabeth!
And I put chewing gum in everyone's hair!
How evil am I?!
Hands up in the air!
Hands up! And...
Hands up! Oh, yeah, yeah!
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
Help! Help!
My cuddle list, you should kill her!
She's so strong! Oh!
Liz, Liz has fallen!
Oh, come on, come on up. Up, up, up.
It's okay, it's okay, you did great. You want another go?
Okay, okay." "Whoa!
Oh, no, I've fallen!
I'm doing it..." "Did I win, Liz? Did I win?
Okay, okay. All right." "Did I win?
Are you willingly going to come with me to the police station?
Oh, no, 'cause I'm evil. I'm going to go burn a village.
Wait, stop!
Huh? Look at this!
Oh, my goodness!
I am evil and she's evil. She's the most evil!
Oh, my god, is that a signed picture of the evil, evil, evil Nerissa?!
Yeah, she signed for you!
Give it! I need it!
If you come with me, I'll give this to you!
Oh, yes! I will, yes, yes!
Okay, hands behind your back, hands behind your back!
Yeah, I get the picture though, right?" "Yes, of course! Here you go!
You were playing dirty! You just humiliated Liz!
No, I am a smart, smart cop!
And instead of using violence, I used my brain.
Justice, losing!
I don't know what you're on about. Yeah, yeah, you did really well.
I think you did great. You, uh...
You know, used a weapon against, uh, your... the suspect...
...to, uh, apprehend... apprehend... apprehend them.
And, uh, yeah, so I think you did great.
Um, yeah, great job, Cecilia. I think Cecilia has done the best out of everyone, personally.
You can't do this! You can't film this! I'm requesting...
See? Justice's greatest weakness!
No! No! They weren't supposed to win! Justice is lost!
We're never gonna catch up to Lady Eleanor!
How to Protect JUSTICE! Interrogation Training
[Title: How to Protect JUSTICE! Interrogation Training]
The second training is... Interrogation!
...process,
where even the slightest inconsistencies
in a statement
must be detected to get closer to the truth.
Can Justice remain unaffected by the situation
and accurately draw out the information?
Yeah, I'm the best, actually.
I have a gun...
...and I know how to use it, so...
Easy! Don't worry about it.
I have my ways.
I've been here for so long.
It's going to be the easiest case of my life.
No, I don't think so.
Because my heart is too pure,
and my ass is too fat.
And I'm not a gaslighter like Cecilia Immergreen.
I'm not very confident, but I'll do my best.
Well, well, well, like the criminal!
We are about to begin your interrogation!
Wait a minute. I'm not a criminal.
Why me? I haven't done anything.
What exactly have I been accused of?
Th-That would be the...
...suspected identity fraud...
...and the unlawful acquisition...
...of Nerissa Ravencroft!
I don't know anything about that.
I'm Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame, not Nerissa Ravencroft.
Have you ever seen Nerissa Ravencroft?
You know who Nerissa Ravencroft is?
No, I've never seen her in my life.
Blue-black long hair...
...red eyes...
Tell her that we saw her photo.
If I ever saw such a maiden, I would call her luscious.
She sounds like one.
We have evidence! We have evidence!
We have evidence.
Does the name "nightyniteX3xD" ring a bell to you?
Oh, yes. Because...
..."nightyniteX3xD" is me.
Aha!
I knew it!
You are the prime suspect in the stalking incident!
Of Nerissa Ravencroft?
Go, Gigi, go! Attack!
We have it on paper right here!
And we have all the chat logs that you put in Nerissa Ravencroft's channel right here!
I don't know... I watch her streams for entertainment.
"Nerissa Ravencroft, I'm outside of your house right now."
"Nerissa Ravencroft, I see you from the window."
"Nerissa Ravencroft, take off your shirt."
Whoa, now. That wasn't me!
We also have pictures from the phone!
I don't know about that. I think you're mistaken. I would never speak that way to a princess.
Tell her that we're never gonna give her donuts ever again!
And you will never have donuts ever again!
And I would have never... donuts?
How did you know I like donuts?
No more donuts! No more donuts!
But... but if you just confess...
...we have an in with Nerissa Ravencroft!
Offer her a good deal! We can give you what you want!
A date with Nerissa Ravencroft!
Okay, now you guys lose control.
Look, I admit it. I know who...
Answer us right now! Answer us right now!
Go crazy! Go crazy on her!
I'm scared! Hey, you! Woah...
A fine woman! It is my lucky day!
Chief Raora! Oh, Chief Raora!
What do you guys think you're doing, huh?
I was doing what you were saying.
You useless! You don't do...
...anything in this place!
Why did I hire you, huh? You're so useless!
This person... we have all the evidence...
...and you still didn't manage to make her tell the truth?!
Chief, we're trying our best, okay? We are underpaid!
Overworked! You're embarrassing us in front of the criminal!
Well, maybe you should do better than this!
You're not even listening to me, are you?!
We never fixed our coffee machine!
And we never get paid time off, Raora!
Well, if you work more, maybe you will deserve your coffee machine!
Do you like coffee?
No.
Well, what do you want from me?!
I want infrastructure and workplace equality!
You know, one of my favorite VTuber entertainers, Cecilia Immergreen, she does not like coffee.
Do you remember what did you do in ENReco?
Um... I mean, I make up my own stories in my blog.
Well, your own story with Nerissa Ravencroft many times?
Get her, Boss! Get her, Boss!
Okay, Boss... I think you're all obsessed. I'll leave it to you guys.
Yeah, I think you're doing great.
Thank you. Thank you.
So you do know Nerissa Ravencroft!
I know that her name spelled backwards is "as I win".
How do you know that? How do you know that?!
Uh, I know many win-winners because I'm very popular with the ladies.
Oh... What about the photo collection she has in her room?
We have some things that I want to show you, okay?
See this paper right here?
Are you loose on my shackles, please?
These are all the photos that we found in your room...
...that you have taken of Nerissa Ravencroft!
Do you recognize these photos in Nerissa Ravencroft's...
...room? You took them. We found them on your camera.
I think my mother, where we work, took them at Nerissa Ravencroft's.
It was not your mother!
Oh!
There's a selfie right here!
Oh.
Right there! That's you!
See? It's you, it's you!
So, what do you have to say?
Is that you or is that not you?
I think there's an impostor here.
What about the evidence that we have?
The bra with the wrong size! So it's not hers, it's from Nerissa Ravencroft, because it's also signed by her!
We found a bra in your room...
...and it's the wrong size.
I checked your breast size when you came in, and it's not this size!
Not that one! It is Nerissa Ravencroft's!
And it's also blue! Tell her that it's blue, she never wears blue!
And we know you don't wear blue bras!
I do! You sure you know?
I think you guys should ask...
Stop! Stop, criminal!
I mean...
...we can give you more than a bra from Nerissa Ravencroft.
Help me!
We can give you way more than a bra from Nerissa...
Help!
Did you find out? Did you find out?
It's me!
That's why.
What are you doing to her?!
What did you offer just now?!
You were not supposed to be bribed!
You forced me! It was all her!
Time to get away!
What are you talking about? She was talking about...
...a bra! She was trying to bribe you!
We are not fine... trying to find a new victim.
You made me do it!
What are you doing?!
Why am I even paying you right now?!
All she did was get yelled at...
It's my first day on the force, and I just really wanted to be a good cop!
And then 99X3XD...
And this is true, cause we had all the evidence and all!
And Nerissa doesn't even steal!
I've never seen such a thing. 99X3XD was just...
...so cunning and... that was kind of attractive, actually.
Those long hair, and...
...those curves.
I should go find her.
Oh, they're totally useless. They can't do anything.
I need to find new people for this job.
They don't have the guts for this.
Yeah.
But 99X3XD...
She said that she likes...
...ladies and stuff. Maybe she will like me. Maybe she could work with me, who knows?
Hmm, what is she, anyway?
Ha! They didn't see it coming.
They didn't know I was a... well...
They did know I was 99X3XD.
But they didn't crack me one bit.
For I am too good, I am too cunning,
I am too, too powerful, as they say.
Can I get out of this?
The next training is... Firearms Training!
What's required is precision and split-second judgment.
A moment's hesitation can greatly impact the outcome.
Can Justice remain unfazed by the situation...
...and deliver highly accurate shots?
Firearms training, let's go!
Let's go!
Yes! Let's go over the rules!
A variety of targets will appear one after the other.
Your job is to quickly decide whether to shoot or hold your fire!
If it's a valid target, take it out with your revolver.
But be careful! Not every target is meant to be shot!
Out of the 10 targets, three...
...are no-shoot targets!
So don't let your guard down!
Okay! Okay! I got it.
What do you mean? I wasn't listening.
Don't shoot everything.
No!
Okay, shoot everything! Did you not listen to what I said?!
And most importantly, shoot your friends.
What the freak?!
Aye aye, sir!
Cecilia, you're up first!
Just like that!
Justice, shoot 'em down!
Shoot 'em down, shoot 'em down!
Cecilia, are you feeling confident?
Really good! Look at my... Oh, yeah, I'm really good!
I'm gonna shoot everything, and I'm gonna win!
Ready... set...
Go!
Oh, there it is!
Shoot me! - Yeah!
She's crazy!
What? Oh!
Oh my god, is that a gnome?
With magic... damn!
You killed him! Fairy mushrooms?
Magic fairy gnome.
Is that a pizza? Shoot the pizza!
Pizza's a good thing, though!
Wait, we're supposed to shoot the pizza?
Oh, no!
Don't shoot! No!
No, she was just a little girl!
Die!
She was just a little girl!
That's a Royal Guard! Cecilia!
Ooh, she's a killer.
He's texting while driving!
Good, good! We got rid of a criminal.
Hey, that's my pension!
Oh yeah, shoot that! Shoot her pension!
My pension!
Hahaha!
Hello, tiny jet pack!
Yeah! That's a shot!
Is that... a cucumber?
A cucumber! Don't shoot the cucumber!
Yay! Wait, yeah, we...
Don't shoot, he's eating the royal cookies!
That's how I feel!
I did it!
You shot everything! Yay!
Cecilia's final score is...
Seven points! - Seven?
Sick seven! - Hey, why'd I...
Well, even if I... Honestly?
I think the cucumber was a minus, and I thought it was a plus...
...because we want to kill the cucumber so she doesn't have to eat it.
I don't like cucumbers, right!
And I think even if I shot the ones that weren't meant to shoot...
...sometimes in a crisis situation, you just have to make a decision...
...even if it's the wrong one! - I'm not sure about that!
All right, let's go! Flame on!
All right.
Three, two, one, go!
Yeah!
Okay. Shoot it, shoot it, shoot it!
Ah, she's a true leader.
Shoot it, shoot it, shoot it!
That's me! That's me with a mustache! How can you shoot yourself?
Well, that's obviously not...
No, no, that's a bad, that's a bad...
Now, that's a nice bud.
Oh, yeah. Haha!
Shoot it again! Shoot it again!
Whoa, did you shoot your head shot? Even with the mustache, you do that!
Okay. At fine point...
Look at that swagger, though! Wow!
Is that Henya on the ground?
What's she shooting now? What's her...
My pension! We need turned-in...
Shoot it! We need that for Justice!
My pension! My pizza!
I'm hungry! Shoot it!
Yeah! PBT got...
Okay, money, money!
Money! Shoot that! We need money! We earned money!
Money! What? Why?
We need money! What?
Oh no, Liz.
Oh, kill it! Oh, that's a cat!
Kill it, kill it, kill it! That's so fatty, though!
Shoot me! Shoot it, shoot it!
Hi there!
Girls, don't!
Yeah! So good! Okay, you are done!
Oh, yes! Okay, what is my score?
And your points are... drumroll...
Nine points!
No points?
Nine points! Yay!
Nine points! Wow!
Flame on!
Your aim is so bad!
She's down, no! Don't look!
How are you feeling, Gigi? Are you confident?
I'm confident! I'm confident!
Three, two, one, go!
Oh!
Huh? Oh, cute! That was a...
How could you? That's not real! The gun's not real!
The gun's not real! Money, money, money!
Get the money! That's not real!
Yay! Money! Yay, money!
Money, money, money, money, money!
Money, money, money! Perfect! We need money!
We need money! I had to kill her, she's ugly!
Yes! That was just a baby!
Kill the baby! That's dead.
Get the dead guy! Kill it, it's so tiny!
Kill it! Yay!
No, death box!
Oh, it's flying! GG, no! GG, no! No, death box!
I can't hit it! Oh god, I gotta get a little bit closer.
You're lucky, you're lucky! You're so lucky right now!
Oh no! Kill it, kill it, kill it! Kill it!
I can't kill it! I looked into its eyes and I can't kill it!
I looked right into its eyes and I couldn't do it!
Death box! Yeah! It's dead!
No more pizza! No more pizza diet!
Wow, he's stealing the real cookies! Kill him, kill him!
That's not a real gun! That's why it doesn't work!
Oh, he's texting while driving! Oh my god, we have to put him down!
That's so not good! Okay, I think you're done!
Okay, you're running out of bullets now. Shoot yourself!
Oh no! No! Okay! All right, lineup reveal!
Lineup reveal! Gigi's score!
Okay, the final score for Gigi is...
Do it! Shoot the gun! You... I'm so tired of you!
Hey, she got 8! She got 8! Yay!
It's your girl, Raora Panthera! It's me! Yeah, big cat means big gun!
Me? Yeah yeah, okay, let's go!
Let's face the gun... It's not real! I practiced!
What do I do again? You'll see targets and you shoot the ones that are bad! Bad targets!
Bad ones? Bad, only the bad ones. How do I know which one is bad?
That's up to you to decide as a member of Justice.
Ready? Ready? Set... go!
Okay, get... oh! Are you gonna shoot?
I'm not gonna shoot that. It's right there, Raora! A little to the left!
Raora, you're supposed to shoot this one! No, it says 'shoot me', it's a trap!
Get him! He's texting while driving!
Get him! Get him, he's...
Oh god! That guy's a menace!
Liz? Liz?! Don't kill Liz!
I'm right here, Raora, that's an impostor! You killed Liz!
Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
Okay, I got it, I got it! What the hell? No! That's a bad...
Raora with the god eyes, huh? What kind of god eyes are those?
Get him! He's stealing the cookies! But it's not good...
Why didn't you kill the guy with the cookies?!
All right, come on Raora, you can get the next one! Get the next one!
Aw, cute! No, he's evil! He's stealing family heirlooms!
Oh, he doesn't... Hey, I thought these were bad!
You guys know... Ah! Kill it, kill it, kill it!
No, it's cute! The egg with the face...
Oh, death box! Death box! Yeah!
Get it, get it, get it! Cleanse the world!
Jump back! Jump back into team!
Eww! Pickle!
Oh, it jumps real high! Cute cucumber!
Wait, but why a cucumber?
Yay, cucumber for dinner!
Oh, money! Money! Do we want money?
No, we don't want money. We have the GG tax.
Yay! I sucked!
That was great! That was crazy! That was really good.
Maybe I can do something else instead. Maybe I can find criminals!
Gigi, do you want to say the score? I'll say the score, Raora!
Do you want to know how much it was? Do you want to know?
I know... Hold my hand, I need to tell you. Hold my hand.
It was... 4!
4?! Justice is 4! You did that on purpose because there's 4 of us!
Raora, you're so clever, Panthera! Justice!
And with that, the training is complete! Huzzah!
Yeah! And the winner is... Elizabeth!
Ah!
Look at the loser! Loser!
Look at the loser! Look at her! Oh, she's a loser!
You're a frickin' loser!
I just wanted to make you win because I'm the strongest with my God Eyes, so...
Look, see? That was good. What's that behind my back?
What's that behind your back?!
You can't do that!
She's crazy!
Gigi! Gigi!
The next training is: Traffic Enforcement Training.
This duty requires accurately assessing the violation and processing it correctly.
However, in the field, unexpected behavior can sometimes shake an officer's judgment.
Can Justice stay unfazed in any situation and carry out the appropriate response?
We did a voice! Good job, my goon! Look out, we've got police right now!
My goon, goon, do the voice! Do the voice! -Okay, boss.
Buonasera. -Good afternoon.
How's your day? You know what? I'll pull you over.
That was really cool!
Oh my God... -Silenzio!
Don't act like you don't know anything!
You blew right through the stop sign!
We're just... You're really in your early right now... -We're in a rush!
My husband, he's pregnant!
Can I see your driver's license, please? -Ah, yes, yes...
Do you have your driver's license?
We don't have time! He's really pregnant! -I am so pregnant!
His water just broke!
We have to go to the hospital! -Oh my God, we have to go to the hospital right now, please!
I think they're lying.
We're not... We're not lying! He's like... really pregnant!
Look how big he is! -I think she's not pregnant.
Excuse me, my husband is really pregnant, he's really big right now.
I'm really pregnant, please...
Let me feel the baby.
It's kicking! -I don't know, can you not feel it?
My son! I feel you!
Your elbow! -Silenzio!
Please... Don't you think those two are acting a little bit suspicious?
Mamma mia...
Are you alright? Do you think... could it be...?
Yes! See? This is exactly what I was thinking!
My son! No, no, no!
You are stopping us because I am pregnant! -What was that?
That was the baby! -It was the baby!
There was a horse in there! -No, it was my baby! It was our baby!
Did you give birth recently? -It was our baby!
No, no, no! I heard a squeaking coming from the trunk!
Hey, you can't say that about my baby!
Mind if we take a look? -I do mind! I mind!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
We're just gonna take a look at that trunk.
Please! Please! -You are definitely guilty!
No, you can't! You can't! -Freeze! Police!
You'll stop me! -It's a horse!
A horse?! -It's a horse! It's my son!
It's ours! Gigi Murin! Cecilia Immergreen!
You're under arrest!
No, wait! You're taking me! -You are arrested!
I can't be under arrest! I have too much to live...
Yeah, you're under arrest! Give me your hand!
You are arrested officially!
Wait, Boss! Boss! You can't leave me!
I'm outta here! See ya later!
We're going to get her! Get her!
Let's get her! I can't drive!
It's just you and me, baby.
Alright, the place is empty.
Got about 10 minutes before the guard's next patrol.
So this is the YAGO trophy...
The Giga-Mega National Treasure.
I'm gonna make a fortune on this.
This is Justice. Is this an emergency?
Help, please! Please...
Please somebody answer me, please! Oh, I don't know what to do!
Calm down, and take a deep breath.
Can you tell me exactly what happened?
Uh, calm down... calm down...
Leave it to us! Leave it to us!
Justice is on the way right now!
Everyone, we have a case!
The ultimate national treasure has been stolen!
Head to the scene immediately!
The ultimate national treasure?
You mean the YAGO statue?
Who'd even want that? Just let him keep it!
Gigi! That is disrespectful!
It is STILL the ultimate national treasure!
We're counting on you.
Yeah, fine, I'm on it.
Aww, wait, Liz!
The super limited edition Sweetie Plastic drops in just 3 minutes!
It's limited quantity, okay? That means I absolutely have to buy it!
Okay, so, only 2 minutes left now...
Just GO already!
Huh, no! Oh, mamma mia! Fortissimo!
Cecilia, did you get any information?
Cecilia!
Hold on! Who the hell changed the keymap on my keyboard?!
Glad you loved my present, Cece!
Was that you?!
You absolute garbage can! When I get to you, I'm going to...
Cecilia, every second counts here!
I know, I know!
All right, I found a backdoor in the palace hub, cracking the encrypted protocol via brute force,
enforcing the security patch overdrive on the mainframe system security data...
In English please!
Uh, fine. Uh, I mean, the suspect is a woman dressed entirely in black...
Height looks around 168 centimeters.
She really likes people wearing helmets!
Ah! She's fleeing north! If you move now, you can still catch her!
You all heard her! Let's move out and apprehend the suspect!
For Justice!
Raora, what are you doing? You're not even driving! You don't know how to drive a car?
Put your foot on the gas pedal!
Wait, stop! Wait, what?
There is a horse in front of us!
Oh my god, there's a horse! A horse right there!
There's no freaking way...
No way! Is that real?!
How am I supposed to get out of here now?!
Am I gonna be able to buy limited edition Giardiniera if I don't make it in time?!
In time!
Horses like vegetables, right? I think there's a cucumber in the trunk.
A cucumber in the trunk for the horse!
Hold on, Cecile! Why do you have a cucumber in your pocket right now?
Cecile, you know I hate... You know why!
You know why! What?
Cecile, you know I hate cucumbers! Why do you have cucumbers right now?! Ew!
Get out of here! You know where I'm gonna put the cucumber?
Get out of here right now! I don't wanna see that cucumber! Ew!
What about for the horse? No! You hate me! Don't you fucking hate me?!
You hate me! So you hate me! So you hate me!
Just say it! Tell me! You know how I feel when you tell me that you bring cucumbers!
And I bring cucumbers! And I know that I hate... I hate the taste! Everything about cucumber!
We talked about that many times!
Those two are away with the fairies.
Cecilia! Do you have any updates on the suspect's location?
So close!
Cecilia? Cecilia...
Cecilia Immergreen!
No! I missed! Look what you did, Liz! You ruined my perfect score! I was so close!
Not you, too!
Did I fail them as a mother?
My heart breaks as their big sister. I've done everything in my power to look after those three...
Those three wild, eccentric little sisters...
And guide them to this very day. I gave them my all!
Oh, what did I do to deserve such cruelty?
Where did I go wrong? Where did my guidance stray away from the path?
You three were still... still there, huh?
We're sorry...
I promise I'll be a good girl. Big sister!
Big sister! Big sister! Big sister!
It's just allergies. I'm not crying. You're crying.
Thank you, Big Sister! I love you, Big Sister!
Happily ever after... Justice, just like that.
Justice can't catch up!
Guys, everyone!
It's the thief who stole the Ultimate Yagoo Statue!
We're gonna kill them! What the freak? Kill them, kill them!
Hey, you! Hold it right there!
Because of you, I missed out on limited edition Giardiniera and I didn't even get to eat my delicious pizza!
How are you going to take responsibility for this?
That sounds like a you problem. Go eat your pizza now.
Oh, by the way, there's a shop nearby famous for its cucumber pizza. It's to die for.
Cucumber pizza?! Ew!
Even I've had it before. Absolutely exquisite!
This is... This is such an insult!
Impossible!
It's okay. Relax, relax, relax.
Doom!
Doom? Doom? Doom?!
Justice Shopping!
And now, it's time to introduce Justice's 2nd Anniversary Merch!
First, take a look at this: The Premium Acrylic Message Board!
We spoke with someone who actually used it.
...to talk about the Premium Acrylic Message Board?
Ah, yeah! Yeah, sure! Oui, oui!
Ah, this artwork is so cool! I love it so much!
Ah, using acrylic instead of paper was such a good choice!
And it makes it feel really special!
And the foil stamped replicated messages...
...that's honestly the best part!
I can't stop looking at it!
It just looks that much good, you know? Oui, oui!
Ah, please support Justice and buy their merch!
Oui, thank you! Merci!
Wow! That's some pretty high praise!
We've still got lots more merch to introduce,
so let's move on to the next item. Here it is!
Embroidered Patch Keychain!
So cute!
The illustrator behind this artwork...
...is none other than Raora Panthera!
And guess what? We've received a special message directly from her!
Tada!
This is Raora Panthera, the artist behind the embroidered keychains!
Rawr!
You know, I'm so happy I got the chance to draw for my Justice girls!
Creating something for my friends always feels really special.
And I hope you're gonna love them as much as I do!
Yes, yes, yes!
And you know, they took all my adorable illustrations and turned them into those cute embroidered keychains!
And, you know, since they're keychains, you can attach them to your bag and take them with you wherever you go!
Yeah, a little bit of extra cuteness for your everyday life!
So make sure to pick one up!
And trust me, the cuteness is guaranteed!
Yes! Look at that! They're so cute! Adorable!
What a wonderful piece of merch!
Anyone would love to have that one in their home, including me!
Oh, right! Let's move on to the next piece of merch.
Take a look at this!
The Medal-Style Badge!
Cool!
We caught up with Justice's leader, Elizabeth, to get her thoughts!
Hmm?
You want to hear about the badge?
Of course, my sweethearts, my Just Chads.
This badge was designed with the image of law enforcement and authority in mind.
The weighty, prestigious look fits Justice perfectly, don't you think?
I think it looks absolutely fantabidosy! It looks fantastic! Very cool.
Anyone who strives for justice should definitely get their hands on one.
Oh, and it also comes in a beautiful display box, so it's perfect for displaying and admiring as well.
I hope when you guys look at your medal or wear it,
that you will remember how us Justice are so proud of you all and we all really appreciate you so, so, so much.
So I really hope that comes to mind every time you wear or look at this medal.
Mwa!
And that was a message from Elizabeth!
And now, for the final item we're introducing today...
Here it is!
The Double-Zip Patch Hoodie!
Whoa!
We spoke with a fan who actually got their hands on the merch!
Wait!
A Justice show?!
Oh... Oh my god! Oh my god! I'm so excited!
You want to hear...
...my thoughts on this merch?
As the biggest Justice fan in the world that has nothing to do with Justice, I'm just a random fan passing by... Of course! Ask me anything!
[Q: What do you think about this item?]
Oh, I absolutely love the design!
The patches inspired by all four members of Justice are so cute and stylish!
And I love how each one of them reflects their personality!
And the logo and the text on the back give it such a cool, premium look!
It's the kind of hoodie that instantly makes you think...
...'mm, yes, this is Justice!'
[Q: How is it when you actually wear it?]
Oh, it's amazing!
The brushed fleece lining makes it super warm and comfortable!
Not only does it look great, but it's also really practical!
And the fact that it comes in both L and LL sizes is fantastic!
I think a lot of fans will appreciate having different size options,
so make sure to buy the Justice merch, okay?!
Wow, jolly good!
Now that's a passionate fan!
And that's it for Justice Shopping!
So, how was it?
It was awesome!
And what did you like the most?
The horses!
Aw, the horses!
And this Justice new plush!
We interrupt your regularly scheduled programming to bring you this breaking news.
We have just received an exclusive update from Justice, the global guardians of peace.
Rumor has it a brand new track from the iconic four-piece is about to drop at any second.
I repeat, new music from Justice is imminent.
Do not touch that dial.
We will be right back with a world premiere.
This is Ouro Kronii, signing out.
Yeah
Are you there?
You’re a SUPER GIRL
(Justice just like that, Justice get get that)
If you’re feeling trapped, send out a signal right above!
(Gesundheit!)
We’ll find you, set you free then you can sign up for the club!
(In it!)
Danger, fun fun fun
Soul shine like the sun
(Minna Happiness, Minna Happiness)
(Everyone's Happiness, Everyone's Happiness)
The frig? I'm big! My strong strong muscle
They see me run, it's no miracle
You are shining SO BRIGHT!
Do your dancing LET'S FIGHT!
You can be a SUPER SUPER GIRL
I'm the SUPER!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
SUPER!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
Come sing with us, beating villains for fun <3 it
(I'm SUPER GIRL)
Put on your antennas, get your super girl fit
(You're SUPER GIRL)
I'm the SUPER!
DUPER!
SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL
I always want a pizza, stack those fries up to the sky
(Ciao ciao)
You lot say whatcha think about us hittin' town tonight?
(Justice!)
Feeling happy time
No sad, say bye bye
(Motto Maniac, Justice just like that)
(More Maniac, Justice just like that)
So stomp, stomp, stomp your feet to this beat
Cuz we are space, no no gravity!
You are shining SO BRIGHT!
Do your dancing LET'S FIGHT!
You can be a SUPER SUPER GIRL
I'm the SUPER!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
SUPER!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
I know you're feeling so super bad
You don't have depression, you're just super sad
We are change the world, that's hope!
If you doubt, hope you explode!
Justice loud, Justice proud
And we keep telling you!
We are SUPER!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
SUPER!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
Justice we are justice, make the baddies go boom!
(I'm SUPER GIRL)
Come on, come on, baby, rocket ship to the moon!
(You're SUPER GIRL)
I'm the SUPER!
DUPER!
SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL
And that was Supernova Super Girl, our brand new song!
And just like that, our second anniversary stream is coming to an end.
So, what did you all think? We'll start with Raora this time.
Eh, me? Yeah, you first this time.
Huh, me? Yeah, you first this time.
Ah, it was really fun, it was amazing! I can't believe it's been already two years!
I know, right?
Ah, thank you so much, you guys, as well for being the best... the best companions ever, you know!
Yeah!
I'm so grateful to you guys, and thank you to JustChats for supporting us since two years now!
Thank you, JustChats!
Thank you very much, everyone, for being here!
And now-- Oh, sorry!
Do it with me! Do it with me!
Thank you very much for being here today, everyone! Thank you for two years...
...3D Justice!
Yeah!
Please keep supporting us and listen to our song!
Yes! Stream SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL!
Elizabeth, what do you think?
What I think? I think the stage is very cool! Look at this stage! Wow!
And look at this amazing team. I couldn't ask for a better...
...I'm so grateful! I love you all very much!
And just as we love you all very much too, thank you so much for supporting Justice.
Thank you so, so, so much! We love you so much!
So many kisses! You guys are so spoiled! Okay, GG!
Are you eating that? She's eating the camera!
Thanks, chat! Thank you for supporting us for...
...two years!
Two! We didn't even know if we could... I didn't even know Raora could count to two!
Really, really! But we made it to two years!
Thank you for supporting us! Please stream SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL!
Learn the...
...chants! For every song!
Learn the chants! For some reason, maybe you should learn the chants!
I wonder if there's a lyrics somewhere for you to learn when we call SUPERNOVA...
...SUPER GIRL!
Or minna happiness!
Minna happiness! Yeah!
We all feel like super girls because of you guys.
Thanks, overall! Yeah!
And don't forget to grab the merch!
Justice merch!
Yes! Thank you, thank you! Thank you all so much for celebrating with us today!
Please keep supporting Justice, please, going forward as well!
Now then, let's all say goodbye together with our own chant!
Yeah! You ready? I'm ready! All right!
Justice, just like that!
Justice, get get that!
Minna happiness! Minna happiness!
Minna happiness! Bye-bye!
Stay tuned for the premiere of Justice's new MV "SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL" right after this!